A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants, Accession 2015:115 FA1321
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1979-2007; 1
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Towards an Integral Human Sexuality - 09600995, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 232)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Identification and Management of Students Who Are Victims of Violence - 09600995, 2001 May 23-25 (Box 33, Folder 233)
    Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group on Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Forum on Menopause and Andropause - 09600995, 2000 September 29 (Box 33, Folder 234)
    Philippine Health Social Science Association and Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group on Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Voices from Three Cultures - 09600995, 2001 January 18-20 (Box 33, Folder 235)
    Women's Conference on Reproductive Health; Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group on Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Globalization, Migration, and Sex Trafficking - 09600995, 2000 February 25-26 (Box 33, Folder 236)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Reaping the Whirlwind: Travails of the Halaw (Filipino Deportees from Malaysia), Magdalena C. Cabaraban and Ederlinda M. Fernandez - 09600995, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 237)
    Mindanao Working Group on Reproductive Health, Gender and Sexuality
  - University of the Witwatersrand, South Africa - Governance in the New South Africa: The Challenges of Globalisation, Guy Mhone and Omano Edigheji - Final Research Report Manuscript - 10151906, 2002 December (Box 33, Folder 238)
  - University of the Witwatersrand, South Africa - Research Report on Globalisation and Governance: Participatory Local Governance and Development in Post-Apartheid South Africa, Project Directors Guy Mhone and Omano Edigheji - 10151906, 2004 June 30 (Box 34, Folder 239)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - 10001445, 2001-2003 (Box 34, Folder 240)
    Includes: "From the Green Revolution to the Biotechnology Revolution: Food for Poor People in the 21st Century," Dr. Gordon Conway; Middle East Project, September 2001-July 2002
  - The Aspen Institute - Natural Resources as Community Assets: Lessons from Two Continents, Brian Child and Martha West Lyman - Draft - 09700635, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 241)
    A Publication of the Sand County Foundation and the Aspen Institute
  - The Reinvestment Fund - International Leaders' Forum - Indonesia - 10001435, 2002 September 29 - October 4 (Box 34, Folder 242-243)
    Assets/Economic Development (ED) - Attachments
  - Commonwealth Foundation - Citizens and Governance Programme - Annex 1 and 2 - 09950844, 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 244)
    Includes: Tri-Sector Dialogues; Narrative Report to the Ford Foundation; Multi-Sectoral Partnerships for Democracy and Development: The Kampala Vision
  - Parents for Public Schools - 10350435, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 245)
    Knowledge Creativity and Freedom (KCF)/Education, Sexuality, Religion (ESR)
    Sticks in a Bundle: Reflections on Public Education Advocacy; Mississippi Conscience: The Story of Parents for Public Schools
  - Santa Clara University School of Law Center for Social Justice - Race and Justice: Student Workbook, Stephanie M. Wildman - 10251724, 2004 November 15 (Box 35, Folder 246)
  - Santa Clara University School of Law Center for Social Justice - Teaching Race and Justice at the High School Level: A Teacher's Guide, Stephanie M. Wildman - 10251724, 2004 November 15 (Box 35, Folder 247)
  - Hanoi Agricultural University - Center for Agricultural Research and Ecological Studies (CARES) Publications That Have Been Completed With Funds From The Ford Foundation - 10250503, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 248)
  - Viva Rio - The Campaign for the Approval of the New Firearms Control Law in Brazil: "The Disarmament Statute" - 10200839, 2003 July-December (Box 36, Folder 249)
  - Viva Rio - Small Arms International Destruction Day in Rio de Janeiro: Destruction of 10,000 Small Arms and Light Weapons (SALW), 2002 July 12 (Box 36, Folder 250)
  - Support Office for the Movement of Self-Help Initiatives BORIS - Reports - 09900324, 1995-1997 (Box 36, Folder 251)
    BORIS Annual Report 1996; BORIS 1995 Report; BORIS 1997 Report
  - Centre for Democracy & Development - Constitutionalism in Transition: Regional Institutions and Constitutional Development in Africa - 10100724, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 252)
  - CD-R - York University - 10002003 - Encyclopedia of Caribbean Religions - Draft, 2005 November; CD-R (Box 36, Item 2015:115:056)
  - The Trustees of Indiana University - "Nepal Irrigation Institutions and Systems III" - Final Report - Summary List of Publications - 09400518, 1997-2002 (Box 36, Folder 253)
  - Social Science Research Council - "Intellectual Property, Markets, and Cultural Flows," New York - 10350703, 2003 October 24-25 (Box 36, Folder 254)
  - Foundation for Rural Institutions, Economics and Development (FRIEND) - Prospect and Scenarios For the Party-List System in the Philippines, Fermin D. Adriano - 10001711, 2000-2002 (Box 36, Folder 255)
  - The Balm in Gilead - Overview of Organizational Development Activities - 09701777, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 256)
    Asset Based Community Development (ABCD)/HD
  - Isis - Women's International Cross-Cultural Exchange (WICCE) - Documenting the Violations of Women Rights During Armed Conflict: A Tool for Advocacy and Sustainable Peace, Kampala, Uganda - 10300350, 2004 August 23 - September 3 (Box 36, Folder 257)
  - Linangan Ng Kababaihan - International Dialogue on Safe Abortion, Likhaan, Makati City, Philippines - 09901246, 1999 July 22-24 (Box 37, Folder 258)
  - Justice Africa Limited - 10200619, 2002; Digital media in folder - 3 1/2-inch floppy disk - Ford Foundation Papers, undated (Box 37, Folder 259)
    Includes: African Development Forum III "Defining Priorities for Regional Integration" Consensus Statement and the Way Ahead; Symposium on the African Union, Addis Adaba - Statement of Consensus; First African Union Summit: Report and Reflections; Issues Paper for African Union Symposium - The Economic Dimension to the African Union; Issues Paper for African Union Symposium - The Architecture and Capacity of the African Union; Issues Paper for African Union Symposium - The African Union and Peace and Security; Prospects for Peace in Sudan Briefing January 2002, February 2002, March 2002, April 2002, May-June 2002, June-July 2002, August 2002, September 2002, October 2002, November-December 2002; Report of the Directors and Financial Statements For The Year Ended 30 September 2002 For Justice Africa LTD, Trustient Chartered Accountants
    - 3½-inch floppy - Ford Foundation Papers, undated; 3 1/2-inch floppy disk (Box 37, Item 2015:115:057)
  - Council for the Development of Social Science Research in Africa (CODESRIA) - An Intellectual Agenda - 09700119, 1997-2001 (Box 37, Folder 260)
  - CIVICUS - Towards Financial Self-Reliance: A Handbook of Approaches to Resource Mobilisation for Citizens' Organizations in the South, Manila, Philippines - 09801159, 1999 September 21-24 (Box 37, Folder 261)
  - CIVICUS - 2001 Annual Report - 09801159 (Box 37, Folder 262)
  - CIVICUS - World Alliance for Citizen Participation - 09801159, 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 263)
    Includes: Audited Financial Statements and Supplemental Information December 31, 1999 and 1998; Why Did You Join CIVICUS? Voices of Members February 2000; CIVICUS Work Plan 2000-2001 Summary; @lliance Vol. 4, No. 4; The Chronicle of Philanthropy article: A Call for Cooperation in Behalf of the Powerless; Samples of E-CIVICUS and CIVICUSWorld
  - Regents of the University of Michigan - Laporan Penelitian: Edisi Revisi - Petani dan Nasionalisasi: Keikutsertaan Massa Rakyat Tani dalam Proses Nasionalisasi di Jember - Tri Chandra Aprianto - Program Pelatihan dan Penelitian Sejarah 10100550, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 264)
    Attachment
  - CD-R - Center for International Studies - Final Reports - Nicaragua - 10251139, undated; CD-R (Box 37, Item 2015:115:058)
  - Casa Via Magia - Photo Books - 09900720, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 265)
    Includes: Photo Ere and Mercado Cultural Latino Americano, Salvador, Bahia, Brazil, 9 a 15 de decembro de 1999; IV Mercado Cultural - Final Report
  - Casa Via Magia - IV Mercado Cultural - Final Report - 09900720, 2003; Digital media (commercial) in folder - CDs - Salvador - Bahia - Brasil - V Mercado Cultural - Musicas, 2003; IV Mercado Cultural - Salvador, Bahia, Brasil - Musicas, 2002 December 3-8; V Mercado Cultural - Pictures - Salvador - Bahia - Brasil, 2003 December (Box 38, Folder 266)
    - CD - Salvador - Bahia - Brasil - V Mercado Cultural - Musicas, 2003; CD (Box 38, Item 2015:115:059)
    - CD - IV Mercado Cultural - Salvador, Bahia, Brasil - Musicas, 2002 December 3-8; CD (Box 38, Item 2015:115:060)
    - CD - V Mercado Cultural - Pictures - Salvador - Bahia - Brasil, 2003 December; CD (Box 38, Item 2015:115:061)
  - Ecology and Action - Coalición Ríos Vivos Sustentabilidad, Diversidad y Democracia - 10250688, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 267)
    Overseas; Attachment
  - Inter-American Institute of Human Rights (IIDH) - Evaluacion del XXII Curso Interdisciplinario den Derechos Humanos - Consultoria (Evaluation of the XXI Inter-Disciplinary Course on Human Rights - Consultancy), Laura Guzman Stein and Anne Letendre Morales - 09801424, 2004 September (Box 38, Folder 268)
    Instituto InterAmericano en Derechos Humanos XXII Curso Interdisciplinario en Derechos Humanos Derechos Economicos, Sociales Y Culturales
  - Inter-American Institute of Human Rights (IIDH) - XII Curso Interdisciplinario de Derechos Humanos Derechos Economicos y Sociales - Memoria de los Talleres - 09801424, 2004 August (Box 38, Folder 269)
    Unidad Pedagogica Unidad de Investigaciones Aplicadas - XII Inter-Disciplinary Course on Human Rights - Economic and Social Rights - Workshop Memory
  - Inter-American Institute of Human Rights - Informe de Evaluacion de Seguimiento XXI Curso Interdisciplinario en DDHH: Justicia y Seguridad, Laura Guzman Stein and Anne Lettendre - 09801424, 2004 May (Box 38, Folder 270)
  - SaferAfrica - Documentos Basicos Para El Desarrollo de Programas Regionales y Nacionales en la Prevencion, Control y Erradicacion Del Trafico Ilicito de Armas Pequenas y Ligeras en America Latina - 10300948, 1998-2003 (Box 39, Folder 271)
  - SaferAfrica - Manuel des Practiciens sur les Initiatives en Armes Legeres et de Petit Calibres Ayant Rapport a l'Afrique de L'Ouest (Francais) - 10300948, 2003 October (Box 39, Folder 272)
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences (CASS)/Institute of Asia-Pacific Studies (IAPS) - International Conference Paper on East Asian Cooperation: Searching for an Integrated Approach - 10250426, 2003 September 11 (Box 39, Folder 273-274)
    Includes conference paper, programme, list of participants, and brief introduction of participants, and Chinese version of conference paper
  - Women's House of Arica (CEDEMU) - Pamphlets - 10152089, 2002; Digital media in folder - CDs - http://www.mujerculturaysalud.cl - Diseno Sitio Web del Proyecto - "Bases Para Un Modelo Intercultural de Atencion en Salud Sexual y Reproductiva Para las Mujeres Aymaras Del Norte de Chile", undated and Bases Para Un Modelo Intercultural de Atencion en Salud Sexual y Reproductiva Para las Mujeres Aymaras Del Norte de Chile: Un Estudio de Epidemiologia Intercultural, 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 275)
    Includes: Facilitadores Interculturales en el Servicio de Salud Arica: Una Experiencia Intercultural en Salud?, Elias Munoz Gutierrez and Malva-marina Pedrero Sanhueza; Mujeres Indigenas y Derechos Sexuales y Reproductivos: Elementos Para el Debate, Malva-marina Pedrero Sanhueza; Epidemiologia en Contextos Plurietnicos el Problema de los Criterios de Inclusion, Malva-marina Pedrero Sanhueza; Mujeres aymaras y Salud Reproductiva en el norte de Chile, Malva-marina Pedrero S.; Atencion en Salud a Mujeres Aymaras: Percepcion de las usuarias, Elias Munoz Gutierrez and Rossana Testa Salina
    - CD - Bases Para Un Modelo Intercultural de Atencion en Salud Sexual y Reproductiva Para las Mujeres Aymaras Del Norte de Chile: Un Estudio de Epidemiologia Intercultural, 2001-2002; CD (Box 39, Item 2015:115:062)
    - CD - http://www.mujerculturaysalud.cl - Diseno Sitio Web del Proyecto - "Bases Para Un Modelo Intercultural de Atencion en Salud Sexual y Reproductiva Para las Mujeres Aymaras Del Norte de Chile", undated; CD (Box 39, Item 2015:115:063)
  - Helsinki Foundation for Human Rights - 2 Reports - 09801519, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 276, Box 40, Folder 277)
    Attachment; Includes Appendices
  - Sin Fronteras, I.A.P., Mexico - Strengthening Mechanisms for Migrants Access to Justice in Mexico - 10351142, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 278)
    Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights (HR)
  - Adalah: The Legal Center for Arab Minority Rights in Israel - Institutionalized Discrimination Against Palestinian Citizens of Israel, Durban, South Africa - 10100580, 2001 August-September (Box 40, Folder 279)
    Adalah's Report to the World Conference Against Racism, Racial Discrimination, Xenophobia and Related Intolerance
  - Trustees of Boston University - Eco-Ecumenical Foundation of Zimbabwe (EFZIM) - Report on Theological Education and Research, M. L. Daneel - 09900988, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 280)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) - Project Summary and Update: High School Career Academies Demonstration and Evaluation to The Ford Foundation - 09300584, 1998 February (Box 40, Folder 281)
    US International Affairs (USIA)/Education and Culture (EC)
  - South African Institute of Fundraising - The Giving and Sharing Media Launch - Photo Album - 10250684, 2002 October 23 (Box 40, Item 2015:115:064)
  - Regents of the University of Michigan - Crossing Borders: Revitalizing Area Studies - 09701489, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 282)
    Includes: Revitalizing Area Studies Project Report to the Ford Foundation; Identity Formation and Social Issues in Global Perspective: A Workshop Sponsored by The Ford Foundation and the University Michigan's International Institute and Center for Russian and East European Studies, Workshop Papers, University of Michigan-Ann Arbor
  - La Guardia Community College - The International High School - 10101845, 2000-2005 (Box 40, Folder 283)
    Visitor Schedule - Ford Foundation Representatives 2000; Mission Statement; Action Research: The Effect of Portfolio Assessment on Student Achievement Prepared for The National Teachers Policy Institute by Janet R. Price; Correspondence and representative countries; Interdisciplinary Programs at The International High School
  - Homelands Research Group - Border Stories - Correspondence Attached to Final Financial and Narrative Reports - 10000846, 2003 September 1 (Box 40, Folder 284)
  - Observer Research Foundation (ORF) Institute of Asian Studies - Centre for Nepal Studies - Nepal Today - I: A Talk Programme by Prof. S. D. Muni and Personal Impressions of Recent Visitors to Nepal, New Delhi - 10251461, 2002 November (Box 40, Folder 285)
  - The Scribe Video Center - W.E.B. Du Bois Film Project - 09201043, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 286)
    Includes correspondence attached to narrative and financial reports and grant status report
  - Project GRAD Newark - Financial Statements - 10000843, 2000 June 30 (Box 40, Folder 287)
  - Cross City Campaign for Urban School Reform - Making Good on the Promise: High Standards for All - Correspondence Accompanying the Video and Tool Kit on Standards-Based Education - 09800943, 1999 September 17 (Box 40, Folder 288)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations - Policy on International Policy Attitudes (PIPA) - The Hall of Mirrors: Perceptions and Misperceptions in the Congressional Foreign Policy Process - 10451051, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 289)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations - Global Views 2004: Public Opinion and Foreign Policy Media Coverage - 10451051 (Box 41, Folder 290-291)
  - Center for Contemplative Mind in Society - Creating the Contemplative Organization: Lessons from the Field - Preview/Draft Version, Northampton, MA - 10151080, 2004 June (Box 41, Folder 292)
  - American Horizons - Environment Opinion Study (EOS) 1: A Survey of American Voters: Attitudes Toward the Environment: Report and Supporting Data - 09200231, 1990 August (Box 41, Folder 293)
  - American Horizons - Environment Opinion Study (EOS) 2: A Survey of American Voters: Attitudes Toward the Environment: Report and Supporting Data - 09200231, 1991 June (Box 41, Folder 294)
  - American Horizons - Florida Global Warming Project: Report and Supporting Data - 09200231, 1992 January (Box 41, Folder 295)
    League of Conservation Voters Education Fund
  - American Horizons - Environment Opinion Study (EOS) - Focus Group Report, San Francisco, California; Boston, Massachusetts: Report and Transcripts - 09200231, 1993 March 17-18 (Box 42, Folder 296)
  - The Conference Board - Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel (BEST) - Press Coverage - 10000331, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 297)
  - The Conference Board - Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel (BEST) - Report - 10000331, 2002-2003; Digital media in folder - CD-Rs - Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel (BEST) - Marketing to the Geotourist, Michael Seltzer, Director, Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel - Presentation at TIA Outlook Forum, Hollywood, Florida, 2002 October 10 and Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel (BEST) - Community Tourism: Creating Economic Chains Through Partnerships with Local and Indigenous Peoples, Michael Seltzer, Director, Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel, undated (Box 42, Folder 298)
    Sections include: Update, NYC Community Tourism, Community Tourism Summit, Travelers Philanthropy, Think Tank III, Executive Action, Revenue Development, BEST Practice Profiles, Press Clips, Committees
    - CD-R - Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel (BEST) - Marketing to the Geotourist, Michael Seltzer, Director, Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel - Presentation at TIA Outlook Forum, Hollywood, Florida, 2002 October 10; CD-R (Box 42, Folder 298)
    - CD-R - Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel (BEST) - Community Tourism: Creating Economic Chains Through Partnerships with Local and Indigenous Peoples, Michael Seltzer, Director, Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel, undated; CD-R (Box 42, Folder 298)
  - Center for Puppetry Arts - Slides - 10000825, undated (Box 42, Item 2015:115:065)
    Slides of Live Faust, Die Young; The Spooky Puppet Horror Show; The Tales of Edgar Allan Poe; A Midsummer Night's Dream; The Magic Flute, Salzburg Marionette Theatre; The Baroque Opera; Hans Christian Anderson Storybook; XPT; Avanti, Davinci!; Mighty Nice; The Firebird; The Secret Garden; Drumsticks/Fiddlesticks: 3 Works; A Japanese Puppet from Our Museum; New Directions Series Kwaidan
  - Cambridge College - ourCommunity.Net Project - Correspondence - 10000980, 2001 September 25 (Box 42, Folder 299)
  - Common Assets Defense Fund - The State of the Spectrum: The Movement to Reclaim the Nation's Airwaves - 10450888, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 300)
    Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom (KCF)/Media Arts and Culture (MAC)
  - North American Chinese Sociologists' Association - International Conference on Gender Issues in Contemporary China - 09350630, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 301)
    Memos regarding finances and tracking documents
  - National Wildlife Federation - Linking International Trade and Environmental Policy Making - 09800645, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 302)
    Grant award letter and grant tracking/grant information forms
  - Arab Republic of Egypt - National AIDS Program - 09500332, 1995-2000 (Box 42, Folder 303)
    Grant Award letters and Program Action forms
  - Twin Cities RISE! - Workforce Program Serving Low-Income Adults - 09801630, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 304)
    Countersigned grant award letter and program action forms
  - North American Chinese Sociologists' Association - A Conference on Gender Issues - Field Office File - 09350630, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 305)
    Corresponding microfilm: Reel 8816
    Includes signed grant award letter; correspondence; grant application for gender conference; North American Chinese Sociologists' Association, Inc. May/June 1993 Newsletter; Call for Papers; North American Chinese Sociologists' Association Bylaws
  - Harvard University - Harvard Family Research Project - 09300698, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 306)
    Corresponding microfilm - Reel 9049
    Countersigned grant offer letter; Program Action documents
  - Association of African Universities - Strengthening African Universities - 09701101, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 307)
    Corresponding microfilm - Reel 9057
    Contains signed grant offer letter; financial memos; program action forms
  - Rutgers University - Peaceful Resolutions to Conflict in a Multicultural Society - 09700731, 1995-2001 (Box 42, Folder 308)
    Materials from co-collaborators on the initiative: New Jersey Center for Law-Related Education at Seton Hall University and the Rutgers Center for Historical Analysis as well as materials from the Summer Institutes
  - Smithsonian Institution National Museum of the American Indian - Charter Membership Initiatives - Artistic Initiatives - 10000831, 1997-2003 (Box 42, Folder 309)
    - National Museum of the American Indian - Woven by the Grandmothers Exhibition, Montevideo Uruguay - Slides, 2000 March (Box 42, Item 2015:115:066)
  - Hungarian Civil Liberties Union - Narrative and Financial Report and Supplementary Materials - 09800396, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 310)
    Also includes Supplementary Materials: Recognition and Protection of Patients Rights: International Workshop in Budapest, May 19-21, 2000
  - Beijing Language and Culture University - Cooperation and Differences Between China and USA within the Framework of UN, Beijing - 09900758, 2004 March (Box 43, Folder 311)
    Attachment folder
  - Centre for Higher Education Transformation Trust - Manuel Castells Reader - Selected Papers, Reviews, and Interviews - 10000394, 2000 May (Box 43, Folder 312)
  - Charities Aid Foundation (South Africa) - A Family of Concerns - 10450186, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 313)
    Note from an original post-it: 15 NGOs in India - 10101480
  - Campfire Association - The Campfire Programme: An Assessment of Progress - 10350492, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 314)
  - Verification Research Training and Information Center (VERTIC) - The Biological Weapons Convention Protocol: Politics, Science and Industry - 10100196, 2001-2003 (Box 43, Folder 315)
    Includes printouts of webpages, press materials, and Monitoring, Verification, and Compliance report
  - Documenta and Museum Fridericianum Veranstaltungs - Press Releases - 10251885, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 316)
  - Columbia University - Information and Democratic Society: Representing and Conveying Quantitative Data - Photos - 09900685, 2000 March 31 (Box 43, Item 2015:115:067)
  - Manchester Craftsmen's Guild - The Denali Initiative - 09900689, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 317)
    Includes Description of Manchester Craftsmen's Guild: Community Development Corporation (CDC)/Arts Resource Initiative (ARI) and the Denali Initiative; The Denali Initiative - Denali Fellows, 1999; Program Curriculum Cycle One - Session I-V; Pioneer Human Services document
  - The Aspen Institute - National Community-Based Forestry Demonstration Program: Report on the Activities of the Managing Partner, Community Strategies Group - 10000796, 2001 September (Box 44, Folder 318)
  - Slovak Academic Information Agency - Service Center for the Third Sector in Slovakia - Presentation and Meeting of Presidents of Central European Countries - 09700560, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 319)